<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Ada Does</title>
    <link>https://adadoes.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Ada Does</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 22:44:03 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://adadoes.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting a Goal</title>
      <link>https://adadoes.io/post/setting-a-goal/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jun 2018 22:44:03 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adadoes.io/post/setting-a-goal/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s been three weeks since I graduated from RPI. I&amp;rsquo;ve had some time to relax and collect myself, which was something I really needed and has definitely been good for my mental health.
However, I&amp;rsquo;ve come to find that I get anxious very quickly if I don&amp;rsquo;t feel like I am accomplishing something! So I really want to use this time to learn how to maximize my productivity, and in turn maximize my general happiness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introducing BLOG.RCOS.IO</title>
      <link>https://adadoes.io/post/new-rcos-blog/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Jun 2018 19:48:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adadoes.io/post/new-rcos-blog/</guid>
      <description>Something I&amp;rsquo;m very exciting about happened recently! We finally have an official RCOS Blog! This is something we&amp;rsquo;ve wanted to get going for a long time, and finally got around to setting up, thanks to one of our awesome alumni. We have a lot of valuable knowledge and experience about doing and teaching Open Source, and I&amp;rsquo;m really happy that we now have an official channel to share it.
It actually looks really clean too, and is cohesive with the rest of our documentation.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summer of RCOS 1</title>
      <link>https://adadoes.io/post/summer-of-rcos-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 May 2018 18:16:43 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adadoes.io/post/summer-of-rcos-1/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;rsquo;m going to be writing a number of catching-up blog posts about RCOS over the next few months, but I&amp;rsquo;d like to start with the present. We just started the RCOS Summer session today, and I&amp;rsquo;m super excited!
First of all, despite having been in RCOS for nearly 4 years, this is the first time I&amp;rsquo;ve been able to be present on campus for a Summer session. Generally, the Summer sessions are much lighter than the Fall/Spring sessions (by an order of magnitude), and this Summer is no exception.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hello World, And All Who Inhabit It</title>
      <link>https://adadoes.io/post/hello-world/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Mar 2018 00:40:22 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://adadoes.io/post/hello-world/</guid>
      <description>Hello, World!
I&amp;rsquo;m Ada, and this is my blog!
A little about me: I&amp;rsquo;m a software developer, teacher, maker, tinkerer, open source evangelist, and lots of other things! I&amp;rsquo;m currently a senior coordinator at RCOS, the Rensselaer Center for Open Source, which is where I spend most of my time. I love teaching and learning from my peers, developing curriculum, giving talks, and maintaining my open source project, Yacs. I&amp;rsquo;m also involved with MOSSN, the Mozilla Open Source Student Network, where I work with and advise other campus clubs from around the country!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>